[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJS", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Were you tempted to continue down that path and maybe not come into entertainment?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "tempted", "to", "continue", "down", "that", "path", "and", "maybe", "not", "come", "into", "entertainment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Well, initially I was -- when I was 15 I thought I was going to go to law school and I thought that I was going to have a career at politics, most likely, I assume, behind the scenes as a staffer but then my brother, for some reason, decided that he wanted in with show business.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "initially", "I", "was", "--", "when", "I", "was", "15", "I", "thought", "I", "was", "going", "to", "go", "to", "law", "school", "and", "I", "thought", "that", "I", "was", "going", "to", "have", "a", "career", "at", "politics", ",", "most", "likely", ",", "I", "assume", ",", "behind", "the", "scenes", "as", "a", "staffer", "but", "then", "my", "brother", ",", "for", "some", "reason", ",", "decided", "that", "he", "wanted", "in", "with", "show", "business", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "How real is that, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["How", "real", "is", "that", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "It's hard to answer.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "to", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House", "Senate"]}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "What do you think of the current political malaise as many people see it with Washington and almost constant deadlock battle which doesn't achieve anything for the country?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "current", "political", "malaise", "as", "many", "people", "see", "it", "with", "Washington", "and", "almost", "constant", "deadlock", "battle", "which", "does", "n't", "achieve", "anything", "for", "the", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Well, I think we have to start to enter a phase of compromise and reconciliation because with single-digit approval ratings with the House and the Senate and all this stuff that's been going on Wall Street for the last -- you know -- you know beyond -- far beyond 10 years but now they get caught up with their hand in the cookie jar, I think things have to change.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "we", "have", "to", "start", "to", "enter", "a", "phase", "of", "compromise", "and", "reconciliation", "because", "with", "single-digit", "approval", "ratings", "with", "the", "House", "and", "the", "Senate", "and", "all", "this", "stuff", "that", "'s", "been", "going", "on", "Wall", "Street", "for", "the", "last", "--", "you", "know", "--", "you", "know", "beyond", "--", "far", "beyond", "10", "years", "but", "now", "they", "get", "caught", "up", "with", "their", "hand", "in", "the", "cookie", "jar", ",", "I", "think", "things", "have", "to", "change", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "Are you an Obama supporter?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "an", "Obama", "supporter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Most definitely I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Most", "definitely", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "And you know, I put it to her that in terms of ideology of the argument here, what is the difference really for most Americans between being made to have car insurance and being made to have health insurance?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "know", ",", "I", "put", "it", "to", "her", "that", "in", "terms", "of", "ideology", "of", "the", "argument", "here", ",", "what", "is", "the", "difference", "really", "for", "most", "Americans", "between", "being", "made", "to", "have", "car", "insurance", "and", "being", "made", "to", "have", "health", "insurance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJS", "NNPS", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "You know, my opinion on that is, I don't think that they should be forced to have health insurance but if they don't and they are penalized for that, I have no problem with it.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "my", "opinion", "on", "that", "is", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "they", "should", "be", "forced", "to", "have", "health", "insurance", "but", "if", "they", "do", "n't", "and", "they", "are", "penalized", "for", "that", ",", "I", "have", "no", "problem", "with", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Would you?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "What has gone wrong with the American business model?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "gone", "wrong", "with", "the", "American", "business", "model", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "I don't know if I'm -- you know, I'm certainly not an authority and I don't know if I can answer that question responsibly but I -- the economy has shifted.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "I", "'m", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "certainly", "not", "an", "authority", "and", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "I", "can", "answer", "that", "question", "responsibly", "but", "I", "--", "the", "economy", "has", "shifted", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2012"], "LOCATION": ["Paris", "France", "London", "England", "New York", "America", "Beijing", "China", "Beijing", "China"]}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "RBR", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "CD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "I think we have to be careful because there was a time where, you know, Paris and France were at the forefront of everything culturally and politically and then it was replaced by London and England and that was replaced by New York in America and we better watch out or it's going to be Beijing and China and we may look back 50 years from now and say in 2012 it already was Beijing and China.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "have", "to", "be", "careful", "because", "there", "was", "a", "time", "where", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Paris", "and", "France", "were", "at", "the", "forefront", "of", "everything", "culturally", "and", "politically", "and", "then", "it", "was", "replaced", "by", "London", "and", "England", "and", "that", "was", "replaced", "by", "New", "York", "in", "America", "and", "we", "better", "watch", "out", "or", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "Beijing", "and", "China", "and", "we", "may", "look", "back", "50", "years", "from", "now", "and", "say", "in", "2012", "it", "already", "was", "Beijing", "and", "China", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tehran", "America"]}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RP", "RB", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Very simply, what is this about?", "question_tokens": ["Very", "simply", ",", "what", "is", "this", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Well, it's about a gentleman who was growing up in Tehran in the '70s, came to America to be educated, went home, and throughout his education and saw openness, modernization, westernization, democracy, art, culture, freedom, popping up everywhere, glass, shiny, brand new glass buildings, universities all over the place.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "about", "a", "gentleman", "who", "was", "growing", "up", "in", "Tehran", "in", "the", "'70s", ",", "came", "to", "America", "to", "be", "educated", ",", "went", "home", ",", "and", "throughout", "his", "education", "and", "saw", "openness", ",", "modernization", ",", "westernization", ",", "democracy", ",", "art", ",", "culture", ",", "freedom", ",", "popping", "up", "everywhere", ",", "glass", ",", "shiny", ",", "brand", "new", "glass", "buildings", ",", "universities", "all", "over", "the", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "What has been the reaction from Iran to this book?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "been", "the", "reaction", "from", "Iran", "to", "this", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "There's two phases to it.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "two", "phases", "to", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Does that concern you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "concern", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "It concerns me in one sense.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "concerns", "me", "in", "one", "sense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "What is your thoughts?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "thoughts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "You know, it's so dense.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "so", "dense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tina"]}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "And what was it like?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "it", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Well, I was at the Super Bowl with my brother and after the game was over, he was at dinner, and he was looking at an e-mail and he started laughing and he showed it to me, and it's from Tina saying, is it OK for me to make an offer to your brother, actually he's my first choice.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "at", "the", "Super", "Bowl", "with", "my", "brother", "and", "after", "the", "game", "was", "over", ",", "he", "was", "at", "dinner", ",", "and", "he", "was", "looking", "at", "an", "e-mail", "and", "he", "started", "laughing", "and", "he", "showed", "it", "to", "me", ",", "and", "it", "'s", "from", "Tina", "saying", ",", "is", "it", "OK", "for", "me", "to", "make", "an", "offer", "to", "your", "brother", ",", "actually", "he", "'s", "my", "first", "choice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "A good day?", "question_tokens": ["A", "good", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "It was a -- it was a terrific weekend.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "--", "it", "was", "a", "terrific", "weekend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "And, you know, I am excited to see, you know, what half the stakes come down together, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "am", "excited", "to", "see", ",", "you", "know", ",", "what", "half", "the", "stakes", "come", "down", "together", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "PDT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Well, I interviewed him.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "interviewed", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Is that what you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Well, we'll see.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "'ll", "see", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "This relationship Alec has with the paparazzi, which seems to be deteriorating by the -- by the day, what is really that all about, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["This", "relationship", "Alec", "has", "with", "the", "paparazzi", ",", "which", "seems", "to", "be", "deteriorating", "by", "the", "--", "by", "the", "day", ",", "what", "is", "really", "that", "all", "about", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "You know, I'm not sure.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alec"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "What do you think people don't get?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "people", "do", "n't", "get", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "It's hard for me to answer because I think it's all out there.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "for", "me", "to", "answer", "because", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "all", "out", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Did he make a speech in his wedding?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "make", "a", "speech", "in", "his", "wedding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "I -- he did not.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "he", "did", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Any of the brothers (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "of", "the", "brothers", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "NNP", ":", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Because you're all like the celebrity version of the Kennedys, really, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "'re", "all", "like", "the", "celebrity", "version", "of", "the", "Kennedys", ",", "really", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "You know, it's funny.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "funny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 305, "question": "He did?", "question_tokens": ["He", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "The Kennedys acknowledged that like you're the entertainment version of the --", "answer_tokens": ["The", "Kennedys", "acknowledged", "that", "like", "you", "'re", "the", "entertainment", "version", "of", "the", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Are they funny to be around?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "funny", "to", "be", "around", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Hysterical.", "answer_tokens": ["Hysterical", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Your thoughts?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "thoughts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I accept.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "accept", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Or given the way modern celebrity is, with all of the weird new pressures that come with it, would you prefer them to go off and be, you know, a doctor or something like that?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "given", "the", "way", "modern", "celebrity", "is", ",", "with", "all", "of", "the", "weird", "new", "pressures", "that", "come", "with", "it", ",", "would", "you", "prefer", "them", "to", "go", "off", "and", "be", ",", "you", "know", ",", "a", "doctor", "or", "something", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "You know, I -- I would probably avoid -- I would probably prefer that they not go into the business, but I certainly would not be disappointed if they were.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "--", "I", "would", "probably", "avoid", "--", "I", "would", "probably", "prefer", "that", "they", "not", "go", "into", "the", "business", ",", "but", "I", "certainly", "would", "not", "be", "disappointed", "if", "they", "were", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam Baldwin"]}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "What's the worst thing that anyone can say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "worst", "thing", "that", "anyone", "can", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Calling me Adam Baldwin.", "answer_tokens": ["Calling", "me", "Adam", "Baldwin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Is it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "I've got to tell you, I'm not a climatologist.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "got", "to", "tell", "you", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "a", "climatologist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "JJS", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ":", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "What is another explanation?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "another", "explanation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Well, there are folks who are going to be on the side of that we run in cycles on this planet, and because we've only been studying weather for a couple hundred years at best, and then, you know, the -- coming up with the satellite in the '60s would probably be reliable weather records.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "are", "folks", "who", "are", "going", "to", "be", "on", "the", "side", "of", "that", "we", "run", "in", "cycles", "on", "this", "planet", ",", "and", "because", "we", "'ve", "only", "been", "studying", "weather", "for", "a", "couple", "hundred", "years", "at", "best", ",", "and", "then", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "--", "coming", "up", "with", "the", "satellite", "in", "the", "'60s", "would", "probably", "be", "reliable", "weather", "records", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", ",", "DT", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "What is that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Well, there's another good point there, that now we're adding super to just about everything that we have known in weather terminology.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "another", "good", "point", "there", ",", "that", "now", "we", "'re", "adding", "super", "to", "just", "about", "everything", "that", "we", "have", "known", "in", "weather", "terminology", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer", "summer"]}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "What is the most practical, sensible advice for those people who are genuinely concerned now about the heat?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "most", "practical", ",", "sensible", "advice", "for", "those", "people", "who", "are", "genuinely", "concerned", "now", "about", "the", "heat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Let me first say that yes, a lot of folks would be looking forward to a great summer if it were really in summer, and it wouldn't be that unusual.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "first", "say", "that", "yes", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "folks", "would", "be", "looking", "forward", "to", "a", "great", "summer", "if", "it", "were", "really", "in", "summer", ",", "and", "it", "would", "n't", "be", "that", "unusual", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "What were her feelings?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "her", "feelings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Well, she was pleased with the interview and pleased that you appeared to be objective.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "she", "was", "pleased", "with", "the", "interview", "and", "pleased", "that", "you", "appeared", "to", "be", "objective", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "How do you think she will now develop her case to win over public opinion?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "she", "will", "now", "develop", "her", "case", "to", "win", "over", "public", "opinion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Well, I hope that time will do its magic in healing this wound like it does many others.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "hope", "that", "time", "will", "do", "its", "magic", "in", "healing", "this", "wound", "like", "it", "does", "many", "others", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Can you confirm or deny whether that's that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "confirm", "or", "deny", "whether", "that", "'s", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "I can neither confirm nor deny.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "neither", "confirm", "nor", "deny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "I mean, why would you not feel comfortable in confirming or denying it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "why", "would", "you", "not", "feel", "comfortable", "in", "confirming", "or", "denying", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Because I don't the answer.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "do", "n't", "the", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "What has been her reaction?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "been", "her", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "Well, first, I have not read any of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", ",", "I", "have", "not", "read", "any", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "In relation to the specific claim that Casey herself has read these extracts, is that true and what has her reaction been to the Jose Baez book?", "question_tokens": ["In", "relation", "to", "the", "specific", "claim", "that", "Casey", "herself", "has", "read", "these", "extracts", ",", "is", "that", "true", "and", "what", "has", "her", "reaction", "been", "to", "the", "Jose", "Baez", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Well, I can only tell you that as of last night when I spoke with her, she had not seen or had any opportunity to read anything from any book.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "can", "only", "tell", "you", "that", "as", "of", "last", "night", "when", "I", "spoke", "with", "her", ",", "she", "had", "not", "seen", "or", "had", "any", "opportunity", "to", "read", "anything", "from", "any", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Casey", "Jose Baez"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120703pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "And if so, why would you have had issues about her competency?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "so", ",", "why", "would", "you", "have", "had", "issues", "about", "her", "competency", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "It's an account.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "an", "account", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]